{
    "id": "f8347a83d0ac4c73aab03f49ebcd0f37",
    "title": "Join Sentences With Conjunctions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is pretty ............................. intelligent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well",
                "as well as",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1336bd123d92415fba7304a85768b7fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is greedy .......................................... dishonest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "as well",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e98897c761a3434c89857b62faa2d924"
        },
        {
            "question": "God made small things ............................................ great things.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "as well",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5e6f27b0387e4680996e0bfab4e28d51"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither Martin ................................................ his father is tall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43e18958f89048ea8f6a859d37547ee7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is .......................................... honest nor hard working.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "nor",
                "either"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "433cc77e3cba4c179f01c636f79c5e6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................ they gave her the best treatment, they could not save her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "549e7c1d510d43c496b8cffbc82ab502"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ she had the qualifications, she did not get the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c3685045745e4f37b8837b696a2cd4ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ill ........................................... he attended the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "though",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e193044e177a47aba8ca0dd3ecf85275"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... the lawyer defended his client very well, he lost the case.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68b9a9556e404f3eb45d54b882ab0426"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... he is not educated, he possesses practical wisdom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3587df71c29544c7b8d4e1543777cc3a"
        }
    ]
}